Viewers, wherever you are, whatever medium you are using to view us,
whatever medium you are using to watch this programme,
we are with you and you are with us.
Right now, I can see that trouble in your system.
I am saying to that infirmity in your system, in your bones, in your blood, in your kidney, in your liver,
in your muscles, out!
I say I can see them coming out; your sickness is coming out, your disease is coming out.
It is coming out, in your blood! It is coming out, in your kidney!
It is coming out, in your liver! It is coming out! I say, out!
Confess, "Out"!
You disease, you sickness, out. In my liver, tendons, blood, muscles, out!
In my kidney, blood, womb, out!
Confess, out! - in the name of Jesus.
Say, out!
I can see them out. Disease, out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name.
Viewers all over the world, the way out for your career has come - rejoice.
The way out for your finances, business, has come - rejoice.
The way out has come - rejoice.
Confess, "Has come." Say, "Has come, in the name of Jesus."
Say, "The way out for me has come!"
Rejoice, in the name of Jesus.
The way out for me has come.
Begin to rejoice, in the name of Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here, to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and to stay up-to-date with our latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons, and testimonies,
from The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.
CR Robert Begier 8/04/2019